ILGWU. Publications 5780 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 20 Record Vol.III, No.3, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.IV, No.1, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 22 Art Workshop Exhibition, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Twenty Two: Vol. I, No.1, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Twenty-Two: Vol. I, No.2 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Report on the Medical Administration of Sick Benefits to Dressmaker's Union, Local 22, ILGWU, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- A Look Back: Pages Out of American Labor's Past, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Shop Conditions (Box 60, Folder 18)
- The Designer Vol.I, No.1, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- The Designer Vol.II, No.1, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Our Record Official Bulletin Vol.V, No.9, 1941 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Vol.IV, No.8, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Official Bulletin Vol.IV, No.6 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Official Bulletin Vol.IV, No.5, 1939 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Official Bulletin Vol.IV, No.4, 1939 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Official Bulletin Vol.IV, No.2, 1939 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Official Bulletin Special May Day Issue (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Official Bulletin, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Official Bulletin, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Official Bulletin, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Our Record Official Bulletin, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Bulletin Vol.VII, No.2, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Bulletin Vol.VI, No.4, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Bulletin Vol.V, No.3, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Bulletin Vol.V, No.1, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Bulletin Vol.III, No.10, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Bulletin Vol.II, No.2, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Bulletin Vol.II, No.1, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Bulletin Vol.I, No.5, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Bulletin Vol.I, No.2, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Bulletin Vol.I, No.1, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Journal, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Pressers 35 Jubilee, 1938 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Local 35 News Vol.III, No.1 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.III, No.2 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 New Vol.III, No.3 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.IV, No.1 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.IV, No.3 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.V, No.2 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.V, No.1 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.VI, No.1, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.VI, No.3, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.VII, No.1, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.VII, No.3, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.VII, No.3, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Local 35 News Vol.IX, No.1, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- First Annual Dance of the Belt Makers' Union, Local l40, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Tenth Anniversary of Local 46, ILGWU, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- Celebrating the Twenty-Fifth Anniversary, 1941 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Italian Cloakmakers Union Local 48 to ILGWU at its Golden Jubilee Convention, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- 50th Anniversary Gala Concert, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Souvenir Program Cabaret and Dance, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 30)
- Dance, 1938 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- First Semi-Annual Report of the Local 60, ILGWU Health Plan (Box 60, Folder 32)
- Fourth Anniversary Celebration, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 33)
- The Dress Presser- February 1944 (Box 60, Folder 34)
- The Dress Presser- February 1947 (Box 60, Folder 34)
- The Shipping Clerk Vol.I, No.1, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- The Shipping Clerk Vol.II, No.1, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- The Shipping Clerk Vol.II, No.2, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- The Shipping Clerk Vol.II, No.3, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- The Shipping Clerk Vol.II, No.3, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- The Shipping Clerk Vol.III, No.1, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- The Shipping Clerk Vol.III, No.2, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- Testimonial Dinner Tendered to Samuel Shore, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 36)
- Fifty Years, Local 62 ILGWU, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 37)
- Our Union Vol.XXII, No.82, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- Our Union Vol.XXII, No.83, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- Our Union Vol.XXV, No.2, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- Our Union Vol.XXV, No.14, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- Our Union Vol.XXVII, No.1, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- 30th Anniversary Toledo Cloakmakers Local 67, ILGWU, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 39)
- Dressmakers' Annual Ball and Floor Show, 1938 (Box 60, Folder 40)
- Twenty-Fifth Anniversary 1910-1935 (Box 60, Folder 41)
- Thirtieth Anniversary 1910-1940 (Box 60, Folder 42)
- 18th Annual Banquet, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 43)
- 30th Anniversary Banquet Souvenir Journal, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 44)
- 19th Annual Banquet, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 45)
- 20th Annual Banquet Souvenir Journal, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 46)
- Local 85 News Vol.I, No.1, 1056 (Box 60, Folder 47)
- La Nostra Divisa, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 48)
- Libertas Ricordo della Italian Dress and Waist Makers' Union, Local 89, ILGWU, 1922 (Box 60, Folder 49)
- The Spirit of '89, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 50)
- Local LXXXIX XV Anniversary (Box 60, Folder 51)
- Luigi Antonini: His Influence on Italian-American Relations, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Local 89 ILGWU Jubilee, 1944 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Testimonial Dinner Dance, 1934 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Rinascenza Souvenir-Journal, 1930 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Pane E Rosa, 1935 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.I, No.1, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.I, No.2, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.IV, No.1, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.IV, No.2 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.IV, No.3 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.IV, No.4, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.V, No.1 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.V, No.2, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.V, No.3, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.V, No.4, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.VI, No.1, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.VI, No.2, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.VI, No.3, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.VI, No.4, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.VII, No.1, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.VII, No.2 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.VII, No.3, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.VII, No.4, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1 News Vol.VIII, No.1, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- The Spirit of 89-22-1 Vol.VIII, No.2, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- The Spirit of 89-22-1 Vol.X, No.1, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- 60th Anniversary 1913-1973 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- 40th Anniversary Local 91 ILGWU, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- 25th Anniversary Local 91, ILGWU, 1938 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Our Aim Vol.1-8 Bounded Book, 1935-1944 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Testimonial Dinner in Honor of Daniel Nisnavitz, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVII, No.5, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXXIV, No.3, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Local 99 News Vol.II, No.2, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.II, No.3, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.III, No.IV, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.IV, No.III, 1957 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.V, No.1, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.VI, No.1, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.VI, No.2, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.VII, No.5 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.VIII, No.2, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.VIII, No.3, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.VIII, No.5, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.VIII, No.6, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.IX, No.1, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.IX, No.2, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.IX, No.3, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.X, No.1, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.X, No.2, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.X, No.3, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.X, No.IV, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XI, No.1, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XI, No.2, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XII, No.3, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XII, No.4, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XII, No.5, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol. XII, No.6, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XII, No.2, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XII, No.3, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XII, No.4, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XII, No.5, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIII, No.1, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIII, No.3, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIII, No.5, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIV, No.1, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIV, No.2, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIV, No.3 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XV, No.1, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XV, No.2, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XV, No.3, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVI, No.1, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVI, No.2 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVI, No.4, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVI, No.5, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Special Issue, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVI, No.6, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVI, No.7, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVI, No.8, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVI, No.9, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVII, No.1, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVII, No.2, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVII, No.3, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVII, No.4, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVII, No.4, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News, Vol.XVII, No.5, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVIII, No.1, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVIII, No.2, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVIII, No.3, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIX, No.1, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIX, No.2, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIX, No.3, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIX, No.4, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIX, No.5, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XIX, No.6, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XX, No.1, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XX, No.2, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XX, No.3, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 99 News Vol.XX, No.IV, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXI, No.1, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXI, No.2, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXI, No.3, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XX, No.1, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XX, No.2, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXII, No.3, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXII, No.5, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXII, No.6, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIII, No.1, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIII, No.2, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIII, No.2, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIV, No.1, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIV, No.2, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIV, No.3, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXV, No.2, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXV, No.3, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 news Vol.XXV, No.4, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVI, No.1, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVI, No.2, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVI, No.3, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVII, No.1, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVII, No.2, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVII, No.3, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVII, No.4, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XVII, No.5, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVIII, No.1, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVIII, No.2, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXVIII, No.3 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIX, No.1, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIX, No.2, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIX, No.3, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXIX, No.4, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXX, No.1, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXX, No.2, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 News Vol.XXX, No.3, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 99 ILGWU Bulletin 4/27/79, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Local 102 News Fall 1985 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Local 102 News Fall 1984 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Unity News Vol.VIII, No.1, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Unity News Vol.X, No.2 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Unity News Vol.XI, No.2 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Garment Worker Vol.XVI, No.1, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Northeastern News Vol.IX, No.1, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Northeastern News Vol.IX, No.2, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Northeastern News Vol.X, No.2, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- The Common Thread Vol.XI, No.2, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Jubilee Journal: Benjamin Kaplan 60th Birthday, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- The Voice of Local 144, Bounded Copies of Vol. I, No.1 to Vol.III, No.19, 1937-1940 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Plain field Talk Vol.I, No.4, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Plain field Talk Vol.I, No.5, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Union Guide 1934-1938 (Bounded Book of Volumes), 1960 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Knitgoods Workers' Voice, April 1975-November1985, 1975-1985 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Local 163-176 News, 1957 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Knitgoods Workers Voice Vol.XLVIII, No.6, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- ILG-ers are Beautiful Local 178 Pictorial News, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Southern New England District News Vol.I, No.1, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Southern New England District News Vol.I, No.2, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Garment Square Chronicle Vol.I, No.4, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Garment Square Chronicle Vol.I, No.5, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Garment Square Chronicle Vol.I, No.6, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Garment Square Chronicle Vol.II, No.1, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Garment Square Chronicle Vol.II, No.2, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Garment Square Chronicle Vol.III, No.1, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Unity News Vol.I, No.4, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Unity News Vol.VI, No.1, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Unity News Vol.VI, No.2, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Unity News Vol.XIII, No.1, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Unity News Vol.VIII, No.1, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Unity News Vol.IX, No.2, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Unity News Vol.X, No.2, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Round-Up No.3, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Round-Up Local 221 News No.1, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- The Needle's Eye No.123, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- The Needle's Eye No.126, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- The Needle's Eye No.136, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- New Needle's Eye Vol.V, No.1, 1943 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.2, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.3, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.4, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.5, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.6, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.7, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.8, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.9, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.11, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.12, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.20, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.21, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.23, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.24, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.27, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.28, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.29, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.26, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.42, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.43, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.48, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.49, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.50, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.51, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.53, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.55, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.52, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.50, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.52, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.144, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.145, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.148, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- The Needle's Eye No.150, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Pittson Guide Vol.VIII, No.1, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Pittston Guide Vol.IX, No.2, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Pittston Guide Vol.X, No.1, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Pittston Guide Vol.X, No.2, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Pittston Guide Vol.XI, No.1, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Pittston Guide Vol.I, No.2, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Local 351 Union Worker, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Local 351 Union Worker Vol.IX, No.1 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Local 351 Union Worker Vol.IX, No.2 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.16, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.15, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.14, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.13, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.12, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.11, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.9, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.8, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.7, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.5, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.4, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.3, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.2, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pottsville District Reporter Vol.I, No.1, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Bulletin of Local 415-475 Vol.I, No.3, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Voice of the ILGWU Local 415-475 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- ILGWU News Letter No.1, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- ILGWU News Letter No.2, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Sewing Circle Vol.V, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Dedicatoria, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Locales 600 y 601 Vol.I, No.1, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- La Voz de la Union Ano 4, No.13, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- La Voz de la Union Ano 4, No.12, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- La Voz de la Union Ano 4, No.11, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- La Voz de la Union Ano 4, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- La Voz de la Union Ano 4, No.9, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- La Voz de la Union Ano 2, No.5, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- La Voz de la Union Ano 2, No.7, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- La Voz de la Union Ano 2, No.6, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- La Voz de la Union Ano 2, No.3, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- GIDC News Vol.V, No.1, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Rivera Mural, 1942 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Not Guilty, 1915 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Healthcare for All (Box 63, Folder 4)
  English, Spanish and Chinese. 5 copies.
- Stop the Pain! A Workers' Guide to Job Design (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Connie Hayes and Justice, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- The ILGWU: Useful Facts About the ILGWU (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Save Our Health Benefits: We are One in '91, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Constitution of the ILGWU, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Perche' dobbiamo unirci nel '94, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Video Catalogue (Box 63, Folder 11)
- A Brief History of the ILGWU (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Clinton/Gore Torchlight Parade (Box 63, Folder 13)
  English, Chinese and Spanish.
- Moving Towards a Safer and More Productive Workplace, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Catalogue of Literature Available from the ILGWU (Box 63, Folder 15)
- On the Move Fortieth Convention, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Farewell Dinner Given in Honor of Mr. Meyer London, 1914 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- The Retirement Plan: What's It All About?, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Health Crisis Materials (Box 63, Folder 19)
- In Defense of Contractor Limitation and Jobbers' Responsibility Clauses, 1935 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Methods of Price Settlement Under Dress Joint Board, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Comments of Lazare Teper to Conference on the U.S. Apparel Industry, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Rainbows 1995: ILGWU Worker-Family Education Program Chinatown Site (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Student's Magazine '94 The Rising Sun, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Twenty-Fourth Annual Report, 1941 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Report of the Educational Department, ILGWU, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Report: Education Department June 1951-May 1953 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Report to the Educational Committee of the General Executive Board, ILGWU, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Report to the Educational Committee of the General Executive Board, ILGWU, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Education Department Report to General Executive Board, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Signature of 450,000, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- The Story of the ILGWU, 1935 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Students in Action: Site 218, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Summer Post School for Workers, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Video Catalogue (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Welcome! (Box 64, Folder 11)
- "With These Hands" Film Synopsis (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Annual Report 1948: Garment Industry Medical Center (Box 64, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Pamphlets: Bounded Book, 1935-1940 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Pamphlets: Bounded Book 2, 1935-1940 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Reports, 1918 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- First Annual Report, 1911 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Fourth Anniversary Bulletin, 1914 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Six Years' Work and Progress of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control, 1916 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Seventh Annual Report of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control, 1917 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Annual Reports Compiled Booklet, 1915-1917 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Ten Years of Industrial Sanitary Self Control: Tenth Annual Report, 1921 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Twelfth Annual Report, 1923 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Bulletin of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control No.9, 1913 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Bulletin of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control No.10, 1913 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Manufacturers' Bulletin of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control Vol.II, No.2, 1914 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Bulletin of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control, 1914 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Sanitary Control Monthly Bulletin Vol.I, No.1, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Sanitary Control Monthly Bulletin Vol.I, No.2, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Sanitary Control Monthly Bulletin Vol.I, No.3, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Sanitary Control Bulletin Vol.II, No.1, 1920 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Joint Board of Sanitary Control Twelfth Annual Report, 1923 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Fifteenth Anniversary of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control, 1926 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Fifteenth Anniversary of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control, 1925 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- First Annual Report, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- The ILGWU (Box 65, Folder 1)
- The Story of the ILGWU, 1951 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Cases in the Women's Clothing Industry, NY, 1933 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Annual Seminar (Box 65, Folder 4)
- What is the Union? Handout (Box 65, Folder 5)
  3 copies. English, Spanish and French.
- "The Law Says…" Handout (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Catalogue of Literature Available from the ILGWU (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Constitution of the ILGWU, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- 30 Yohriger Yubileum. Rifer Makher Yunion Lokal 17, 1935 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  Yiddish. Cover embossed for David Dubinsky
- General Executive Board Report of the Eleventh Convention, 1914 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Health Services Plan Pamphlet (Box 65, Folder 10)
  Spanish and Chinese. 2 copies.
- ILGWU Journal, 1902 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Souvenir Fourth Annual Convention, 1903 (Box 65, Folder 12)